Wolfgang Reviewer The
second one
is
Iron
Man.
I think that is near
the end of the journey!
THE END
Let's go.
The End
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
What is that, a helicopter?
It's Speedwagon Foundation.
They're looking for a
solid place to touch down.
Speed Wagon Foundation?
They're your associates that are taking
care of Mom in Japan, right, old man?
You're kidding.
We're gonna have to ride in that thing?
No, I wish we could
hitch a ride with them.
But those young men aren't stand users.
If the enemy should attack us,
we'd end up involving them.
Then what is that helicopter
doing here, Jostar-san?
Hmm.
I've requested they bring in backup.
A backup?
He's got a bit of an attitude problem,
so it took a lot of hard
work to get him here.
Mr.
Joestar, it is not possible for
him to accompany us on this trip.
He cannot back us up.
Sounds like you know him, Avdor-san.
Him.
Oh, yes.
Wait a minute.
If he's going to back us up, then
he must be a stand user, right?
Yes, and this stand user is represented
by the tarot card, The Fool.
The fool or do you mean the idiot?
Sounds like his card might
be lacking a little upstairs.
You will be glad he is not your enemy!
You would never beat him, huh?
What did you just say?
You got a lot of nerve
talking to me like that.
It is the truth.
Now take your hands off me.
Knock it off, Victor.
It looks like the helicopter's landing.
Mr.
Joestar, we're glad to
see you're doing well.
Thank you for your trouble.
I appreciate it.
Which one of you guys is the stand user?
Well, which one of you is it?
Huh?
Well, it's actually neither one of us.
He's here in the back seat.
Where?
It's empty.
Yeah, he's there.
What, huh? Who, huh? Where?
What?
Is he a shrimp?
Come out of here!
Whoa, watch out! Be careful.
He's in a really bad mood.
The ride over was pretty rough.
What's this?
I told you he has an attitude problem.
Now step back, Polnareff.
A dog?
Old man, this can't be.
Yes, this dog is the
stand user of the pool.
His name is Iggy, and he loves
to pull and chew on human hair.
Nobody knows where he came from,
and when the animal control officers
in New York weren't able to catch him,
Avdol was called in to get the job done.
Oh, and yes, when Iggy chews on a
person's hair, he has a tendency to fart.
It's a nasty habit.
Get off, you damn dog!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Shut the air up!
What?
What's this? Wow!
I can't cut it!
To put it simply it is a
stand of the sand they say
simplicity is power i'm not
sure i could beat him either.
hey help me get rid of this damn dog
do you have some of his favorite treats?
Yep, there's no way we could
have brought him here without it.
Hey, don't let him see the box!
He has a big weakness for
coffee-flavored chewing gum.
But Iggy is the type who will
never allow himself to be tamed.
What a pain.
At least take off the wrapper first.
How is a dog supposed
to serve as a backup?
Interesting.
A dog who's a stand user.
Here's the food and water you'll
need for the rest of the trip.
These other crates contain medical
supplies and extra clothes.
Thank you.
Before you leave, I'd
like to ask you one thing.
It's about...
it's about my daughter.
How is Holly's medical condition?
Don't hold anything back from me.
Well, I'm afraid I have some bad news.
She's not doing very well.
Your daughter's rapidly losing strength,
and her life is still in grave danger.
According to the prognosis of
the Foundation's physicians,
at best, she has two more weeks.
I see.
We don't have time!
Damn it.
Only two weeks left, huh?
What a pain this is.
I don't know.
Now why is this shitty mud
allowed to be on the seat,
and we have to plant our
asses on the bed of the truck?
My butt is killing me!
Let's just wait until
the gum loses flavor.
As soon as it grows stale,
lure him to the back of the truck with a
new piece of gum and then grab the seat.
God damn you, dog!
Hey, old man.
What's that?
Say, that is in the direction
the helicopter was headed.
No sign of any damage from weapons.
It's almost like it just slammed into
the ground. An accident? Be careful.
It's quite possible this could be
an attack from an enemy's stand.
Over here, it's the pilot. He's dead.
Be careful with him.
You never know what's lurking.
There's scratch marks on the fuselage.
Water?
A ton of water.
From his mouth.
No, from his lungs.
Impossible!
What the hell is going on?
This guy drowned in the
middle of the desert!
But how?
Hey!
Here's the other one!
Are you all right?
Don't move him.
What happened here?
Water.
Mr.
Joestar, here, take this.
Here, my friend.
It's water. Drink it.
No! No!
The water!
It's attacking me!
Ah-ha-ha!
Ah-ha-ha-ha!
It's an enemy stand!
The enemy's stand is hiding
inside the canteen. Damn it.
What's to be gained by attacking those
innocent men from Speedwagon Foundation?
Avdol, did you see what
kind of stand it was?
All I saw was the hand, but it
is still inside the canteen.
I have not seen it come out of there yet.
Jotaro, search for the enemy's main body.
I'm searching for it now.
I can't see the main body anywhere.
There.
Looks like he's controlling
it from a distance,
and the stand seems to be pretty small.
Polnareff, attack the canteen. What?
You're asking me?
Were you even here when the
entire head of the pilot
got sucked through the
tiny hole of the canteen?
If I puncture any holes
in that thing, who knows?
No way!
You're closer to it!
Why don't you just use your emerald
splash and blow it the hell out of here?
I don't want to do it either.
Don't try to get me to do
what you don't want to do.
What kind of twisted
mind do you have, huh?
What the...
It got Kakyoin!
Ah, Kakyoin! Kakyoin!
It got his eyes!
Polareff, don't panic.
Use Chariot to protect
yourself in Kakyoin.
He's gonna lose!
What's going on?
Why would it bother to
attack the pilot's dead body?
No, that's not it.
It didn't go after the body.
It went after the watch's alarm instead.
The alarm.
Then it uses sound to find its targets.
Run for the truck, Baldoref!
Oh, not good.
Hold the rep, hurry up!
Pull him up!
Let's go!
This isn't good.
Yes, we cannot get out of the truck.
Bastard, how dare you
do something like this?
I'm starting up the truck what
Mr.
Joestar, don't tell me
you're running away?
For now, the priority is to
get away from that stand.
Let's go.
The escape by truck.
Evidently, they know now that I and Duel
can detect even the slightest sound.
Although knowing that fact isn't
going to help them too much.
Since our enemy seems to
move by detecting sound,
it can move throughout the sand
without exposing itself to us.
It can attack us from any direction
before we even notice it's there.
And what's worse, the main body
doesn't have to be anywhere near it.
How's Kakyoin doing? It's bad.
He could lose his sight.
We've got to get him to a doctor.
Polnareff!
What's that?
There is water in the club?
The dog it escaped from the truck before
my attack began that could be a problem?
But I'll take care of it later.
Slow down the truck!
Hold the rest.
Chariots.
You asshole!
I'm gonna jump you into pieces this way!
Pull around!
You like that?
Huh?
What the...
what's going on with this... thing?
It combined with more water.
This is very bad.
He will suffocate.
Please stand back.
Magicians, red!
Red boys!
Ballarat, spit the
water outside the truck.
Are you all right?
What do you think we should do now?
Unless we find the enemy's
main body, we're finished.
Old man, the water and the radiator. Shit.
Oh!
Huh?
No one, move!
Do not make a sound.
I know where each one of you landed.
And with the precision of a surgeon!
I shall take you out.
One by one.
What a pain!
This is a very tough stand to fight?
But
This is getting pretty interesting.
Vincero.
I love you, I love you.
Thank you.
Is Is Is